[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
EPISODE 8: A WORLD BUILT ON HYPOCRISY
That'll be 28,300 won.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- You're all set. - Thank you.
Have a nice day.
BROTHER-IN-LAW DID YOU EAT LUNCH YET?
Why here? We could've eaten something better.
If you come to Busan, a pork gukbap is a must.
Actually, I was craving it.
I get to eat it, thanks to you.
Eat up.
You too.
What is this?
A-yeong's tutoring is expensive.
I wanted to help out.
It costs more to live in Seoul.
We don't have to pay rent, and we both work
- so we're all right. - A-yeong is my niece.
I want to do this.
Then we'll put it to good use.
Thank you as always, Eun-tae.
It's nothing.
How is my brother doing lately?
Well...
I'm sure he's doing fine.
He works nights, so we rarely see each other.
Well, I feel bad for him.
He used to be so successful, but now he seems so dejected.
Back in the day
Gong Eun-seok was synonymous with Busan's fashion scene.
He was the first person to bring items trending in Japan
to the Busan market.
Those shabby-looking clothes sold so well.
Yes, I remember now.
The neighborhood went crazy back then.
After he became successful
he bought me Korean beef to celebrate my college admission.
That was my first time having Korean beef.
I had no clue it was that good. It was delicious.
Thanks to Eun-seok
I still have a habit of eating that whenever something good happens.
Was it the barbecue place in Seomyeon?
Yes, have you ever been?
That's where he seduced me.
So the mere mention of Korean beef makes me shudder.
Actually...
Eun-seok asked me for money yesterday.
Again?
I'm so sorry, Eun-tae.
What will I do with that man?
That's not why I'm bringing it up.
He said he wanted to start a business
but I told him I couldn't give him the money.
In my opinion, I don't think it'll do well.
But I could be wrong.
His business might end up doing well.
So in the hope that I'm wrong
I want to help him out how I can.
With that being said
I hope you can accept this money.
Don't hate my brother too much.
He may seem a bit lousy right now
but I still think
he's a great person.
Gosh.
He's a lucky man.
Even in his lousy state, his brother thinks he's great.
At one time, he was the coolest person I knew.
But right now, I think you're the coolest.
Me? Why is that?
You haven't given up on him.
Gosh, what are you saying?
Hurry up and eat.
INCOMING CALL TEAM 4 MR. JEONG SEON-HYUK
Thank you.
How's work these days?
You know how it goes.
It's always the same.
Sure, work is all the same.
So how long will you stay at Hongsung?
I haven't thought about it.
How about some food for thought?
I believe I already rejected your offer.
Our company merged.
I'm no longer the CEO.
Does that mean
you've joined a bigger company?
An article will come out tomorrow.
It'll send quite a shock through the market.
Korea Branch Manager of CGM?
CGM is entering the Korean market.
Based on our predictions
all small and medium-sized brand controllers in Korea will disappear.
It looks like
Hongsung will survive for the next three years
but revenue will be cut by one-third.
All right.
So as Head Brand Manager
you'd have a six-figure salary of at least 100,000 dollars.
How's that?
Is that enough to start thinking about it?
Jeez.
What's the reason?
Do I have to tell you that?
CGM is the best brand controller in North America.
Hongsung is a corner store compared to them.
If you stay there
all you'll get is early retirement.
So why?
When making a decision
one should be most cautious about money.
My worth remains the same.
I should be suspicious if I'm offered more money.
Don't you think
your current worth is being underestimated?
Some people might be getting paid more than they're worth.
I understand.
But I guarantee
you'll regret this moment.
You shouldn't be doing this, Mr. Jeong.
Do you think
you did me a favor or something?
I considered it an insult.
There's something you got wrong.
Do you think Mr. Jeong will be grateful for what you did?
Are you saying you want revenge for that insult?
No.
I'm just doing my job.
CGM called to say they were looking for a Korea Branch Manager.
Someone from Hongsung or a large enough Korean company
who has enough influence as a sole proprietor
but lacks the funds.
I just happened to align with the terms.
Who cares about trivial revenge?
It's just work.
100 DAYS OF PRAYER FOR SUCCESS ON THE 2027 CSAT
Mr. Jang.
What kind of team leader surprises their boss
on a spiritual retreat during the holiday break?
You scared me to death.
I'm sorry, sir.
Anyway, how did you find me?
You weren't answering any of my calls
so I called your house.
Well done.
So is there something wrong?
By any chance
have you heard any news about Mr. Jeong's company?
Jeong Seon-hyuk's company? No.
CGM acquired his company.
CGM?
Are you talking about the CGM we know?
Yes, they plan to enter Korea.
Mr. Jeong is their Korea Branch Manager.
Why are you telling me this now?
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Come on.
You should've started with that.
Well, there's a certain flow to conversations...
Gosh, what is wrong with you?
You're such a strange guy.
I mean, don't you know what's important?
Jeez.
CGM DECLARES KOREA EXPANSION, DOMESTIC COMPANIES ON HIGH ALERT
BELOVED BY HOLLYWOOD, OAULD WILL BE LAUNCHED BY CGM
WHO WILL SURVIVE THE FASHION MARKET'S GLOBAL BATTLEFIELD?
KOREA BRANCH MANAGER JEONG SEON-HYUK
CGM'S AMBITIOUS KOREA BRANCH MANAGER JEONG SEON-HYUK
Jeong Seon-hyuk must be over the moon.
The fact that articles have been published
means they've already finished talks with brands and malls.
It appears they were
strategically laying the groundwork at the three biggest malls.
Right as the articles dropped
they distributed their entire brand list
to shopping complexes and outlets.
Did you get the list of brands CGM is launching?
There are around 300 global brands, as well as some domestic brands.
It basically includes all the brands they control in North America.
They've set the table and are telling retailers to eat up.
Based on Oauld's entry contract
it looks like CGM sacrificed their profit margin.
They're essentially trying to eliminate
all the domestic brand controllers.
If we fight amongst ourselves
malls and shopping complexes will have the upper hand.
And once the weak are eliminated
CGM will monopolize nearly half of the market.
Yes, since the early stage of their expansion
their intention seems to be full domination.
Ma'am, Paradi Mall is requesting an amendment to the Aileye contract.
- Aileye just renewed their contract. - Right.
If we don't renew the contract
they're even willing to pay the penalty.
When Paradi Mall first opened
they clung onto us and begged us to help them open stores...
Didn't they?
Since they begged us
now they want us to beg them.
I doubt they're the only ones.
- Mr. Jang. - Yes, ma'am.
Gather a list of stores and brands where complications have arisen
and give me an initial report by the end of the day.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Gong.
Consult with the Legal Team.
Compare the size of penalties and sales projections and brief me.
You should at least do that to ease your conscience.
Yes, ma'am.
Goodbye, ma'am.
LOIRE OUTLET SCAN-BASED TRADING SALES CONTRACT
Hello.
Gosh.
You should eat a proper meal.
What is it?
Do you need to report on the penalty scale?
Yeah.
JIN HAE-JU
Go back and wait.
I have so many brands to review.
Right, then should I go back?
You probably didn't eat, either.
When you're busy, this is better than a meal.
Just go back and wait.
This is really good.
Let's talk outside.
Are you sure? Aren't you busy?
If you knew that, you shouldn't have come here.
The managing director is inside.
- Let's leave. - Okay.
The managing director doesn't like you.
Says you make problems out of nothing.
That's understandable.
You change contracts as you please.
There's also Mr. Jeong's case.
We dealt with him
but then you helped him, which led to all of this.
You're right.
- Gosh, you really... - So
when can I get the full amount of penalties?
- Approximately. - I don't know, either.
There's no guarantee we can get the exact amount listed in contracts.
We have to compare the time spent on litigation
and the actual amount we can receive.
With all of that, when can I get it?
- Hey, you... - Hae-ju.
I get that it's a struggle, and that you're upset.
But we still have to work.
I need the timeline so I can prepare.
You're really...
If every brand under CGM wants to terminate their contract
the penalty amount in the contract
plus compensation for damages
totals 280 billion won.
Since it'd be a one-sided termination
if we assume it won't go to court and they'll pay up without a fight
the amount would be similar.
Before the end of the day, at least give me an estimate.
I'll report it for now and follow up again later.
I'll get it to you by 5 p.m. Happy now?
Thank you.
But if I were on their legal team
even if it's a one-sided termination
I wouldn't tell them to pay up without a fight.
I'd nitpick and do everything I could to make both parties at fault.
Speaking of which...
Malls have more than enough power to find a way
to make contract termination both parties' fault.
So if they agree to pay the penalty without putting up a fight
that money is coming from CGM.
I'm the one suffering.
Mr. Oh.
Can we talk for a moment?
- Me? - Just a moment.
Mr. Oh.
Has Mr. Jeong offered you a job?
No.
Why, did you get an offer?
Yes.
That bastard...
Would you accept if you got one?
No, I wouldn't.
But I'm annoyed that he didn't even offer.
What about you, Ms. Joo?
Will you accept?
Yes, I'm going to accept it.
He told me to bring you.
- Me? - Yeah.
You see how things are going here.
It's hopeless.
Let's go together.
Do I start right away, then?
I can quit right now.
Don't quit yet.
Why don't you stay here and keep us in the loop?
Be a mole?
Well, things are hectic for all of us.
Did you hear anything from the brand's end?
We haven't heard much, either.
All right, we'll talk soon. Bye.
- Mr. Yang. - Yes?
Should I mark Richard Hansen as backing out as well?
They do have a monopoly in Asia...
- Hang on. - Sure.
Hello, Manager.
What?
This punk's not answering his phone.
Hey, Park Gi-tae.
Mr. Yang.
What are you doing right now?
They asked me to move these.
Who the fuck did? The buying department?
Mr. Yang.
Mr. Yang!
Where's Mr. Kang?
Where is Mr. Kang?
Yes, how may I help you?
I'm from Hongsung's Sales Division.
Did your team tell my staff to haul boxes?
He offered to do it.
Or did I mishear him?
Are you playing games with us over the Aileye contract?
Moving a few boxes won't solve the contract issue.
What an odd thing to say.
- Hey, Park Gi-tae. - Yes.
Tell me exactly what happened.
Well, Mr. Kang said he'd consider the contract renewal
and asked me to help organize the boxes.
And that guy over there
moved a couple of boxes and then disappeared.
Is that true?
Well, yes.
But I didn't do it on purpose.
- I just... - Are you still denying it?
Why are you coming at me? I have no power.
The contract renewal is the general manager's decision.
Exactly.
So I'm asking
why a powerless bastard like you is fucking around with us!
"Fucking around"?
You piece of shit.
- Hey, come here! - Sir, please...
Come at me, motherfucker.
Who the hell are you to order me around?
Let me go. Do you hear what this punk is saying?
That scumbag still thinks he holds the power.
Then do you hold the power? Are you CGM?
A little shit like you throws your weight around?
What a damn lunatic.
We were going to spare a few of your stores, but forget it.
Get rid of all your stores, you fucking bastard!
Who are you to decide that?
Don't spare them, you fucking idiot.
Damn it, I can't take this.
- Let go. - Damn what?
I said, let me go!
- So what? Try me! - You little...
Hit me, you motherfucker!
Go ahead!
Hey, forget it.
Just get out of my sight.
I don't care about your business anymore
- so get lost! - Hey.
I'll leave even if you freaking beg me to stay.
Let's go.
One more thing.
You should call your mother and apologize.
Say sorry for being a disappointment.
Do you understand?
You're nothing but a pathetic fucking loser.
What a piece of shit.
The power dynamic in this industry always changes.
Don't regret it when the time comes.
Remember, you started it.
Jeez, what an asshole.
Gosh, that little...
Why would you just do what that punk told you to do?
I'm sorry.
Moving boxes won't resolve the contract issue.
Let's say it actually does.
That's even more ridiculous.
Will you just keep moving boxes?
This wasn't just you moving boxes as an individual.
It was Paradi Mall using Hongsung International
as their lackeys.
Do you get that?
I'm sorry, sir. I didn't think that far.
You drive, punk.
- Yes, sir. - Jeez.
Hello, I'm Mo Yu-jin of INA Mall's Sales Team.
- Yes, hello. - Hello.
Have a seat.
Wait, 20%?
Yes, as I just told you, 20% for luxury stores
and 36% for regular stores.
You're raising it by 4% so suddenly?
We're not just doing this to Hongsung.
Will these margins also apply to CGM?
Yes.
You're basically telling us to close our stores.
Well, if you can't do it, then that's too bad.
What if we accept your terms?
Will you raise it to 22%?
That's very likely if Hongsung and CGM both accept.
What will you do if we back out?
Will you pay the penalty?
Yes, we intend to pay the penalty.
The contract renewal is just six months away.
But you'd rather pay the penalty?
That's what we've decided to do.
May I speak to your team leader?
They sent me, which is why Hongsung sent you, no?
If my team leader came
then I'm sure you would have sent yours as well.
They want us assistant managers to handle it ourselves.
Don't you get that?
I have to go now.
Let me know when you make a decision.
I'll give you until next week.
All right, then. Take care.
You did well.
I would've done the same thing.
Oh, not at all.
I shouldn't have gone that far.
But I was so angry at the moment.
I'm sorry, sir.
How many times will you apologize?
I'm sorry... I mean, sorry...
Enough.
Over here.
The food's still warm.
- Hello. - We ordered for you.
- Good work today. - Good work, everyone.
Good work, you two. Eat up.
Nice work, Mr. Yang.
What do you mean?
Word has already gotten around.
Mr. Yang of Hongsung called Mr. Kang of Paradi Mall
"a pathetic fucking loser."
Is that all they're saying?
- Not how I verbally destroyed him? - No.
They're just saying you called him a pathetic fucking loser.
Damn, that sucks.
So are they asking for 20%?
Well, yes.
I've never heard of anyone asking for 20% in Korea.
Did CGM really accept those terms?
Will they even make a profit?
Exactly, I doubt they will.
If anything, they'd lose money.
Same with the mall employees. It makes no sense.
Contract renewals are in six months.
Why would they pay the penalty?
They're willing to overextend to increase market power short-term.
Why?
They could easily beat us even if they took their time.
Ji-hye, are you trading crypto or something?
Sorry, sir. I just have to send this one thing.
- What is it? - Laknes sent next season's designs.
I have to share it with Marketing.
- I see. - Show us.
I understand if it's Laknes.
- Should I send it to all of you? - Yes, please do.
Okay, I sent it.
These designs are intense.
I don't get the style these days.
Isn't it too out there?
The extreme designs sell well in China.
That's true.
These days, you've got to sell well in China before anything else.
- Mr. Gong. - Wait.
- Mr. Yang, Mr. Gong! - Mr. Gong.
Mr. Yang!
NAENGMYEON AND BULGOGI PLATTERS
Mr. Gong!
- Where are they going? - Mr. Gong.
Ms. Joo resigned today.
Unsurprising, right?
Over five people have resigned from Sales Division 1.
Team 1's Park Eun-sik also quit.
Park Eun-sik?
They even took a rookie like him?
Well, he claims he's quitting due to a family issue.
After what happened last time
we did our best to crack down. I can't believe this.
Last time was an ethical issue.
This time is a bit different.
Who can stop them from pursuing better benefits?
Even so
they should tell us honestly, instead of claiming family issues.
All right, that's enough.
Let's forget about those who left.
Let them go. We have work to do.
Any new developments since the last report?
Not yet
but I have a feeling there will be soon.
All right.
If any more brands or partners want to terminate contracts
don't stop them. Just report it.
I'm sure some haven't said anything out of morality.
There will definitely be more.
And don't be meek when dealing with the malls.
But if we don't try to stop them, we'll lose 50% of our brands
and 60% of our retailers.
Then what should we do?
Should we beg them to stay?
Won't that just make us look bad?
No need to blame them.
Ultimately, a company must make a profit.
If someone offered me a better deal, I'd take it too.
Did you think they were our friends
because we always shook hands and ate good meals together?
There's no such thing here.
The world runs on that kind of hypocrisy.
Right now
that hypocrisy just feels a bit harsher.
It'll be tough for a while
but our company won't go under from this.
Have confidence.
While we're at it
take everything we moved to shopping complexes and outlets
back to the malls.
- Revert them to full price. - Yes, ma'am.
Does this mean we're giving up on inventory management?
We can't manage the inventory, anyway.
At times like this, we should try to get the penalty fees.
TEAM 5 LEADER GONG EUN-TAE
Yes, what is it?
- Hello, Ms. Park. - Hello, ma'am.
What is this about?
What about CGM?
It's China.
- Because of tariffs? - Yes.
Laknes also entered the Korean market because of tariffs, didn't it?
If they deliver to China from Korea, they can avoid tariffs.
Look, I get the logic.
But it still makes no sense.
Why would they go this far?
There's a rumor going around Shenzhen.
Starting next year
new company establishment
will be heavily restricted in Shenzhen's tax-free zone
That's only three months away.
Yes, they must register their company in Korea and China
secure distribution centers
make initial shipments
and generate sales before then.
Shenzhen grants tariff exemption only once sales are generated.
So once it becomes next year
CGM won't be able to receive tariff exemption.
Have you verified this?
I checked with Shenzhen's Deputy Secretary's assistant.
We can win if we drag this out.
He's right.
If we compete with CGM
and pretend to fight while raising the margin rate
CGM won't be able to hang on.
If they can't enter China's market, there's no need for them
to take on such margin rates in Korea.
There's another option besides dragging this out.
What? You're making me nervous.
What is it?
Let's start with making back our penalty fees.
Why are these punks so confident?
No, we understand your position.
We can only proceed with CGM. I hope you understand.
Then we'll immediately withdraw all of our retailers
upon contract termination.
I hope you know it'll be very hard
to generate this level of revenue in the future.
Damn it.
Don't mind me.
I'll take that.
It's okay. Give it to me.
What a load of nonsense.
Have you made a decision?
Yes.
We'll clear out all our stores.
Sorry?
We just can't accept a 4% increase.
- But... - As for the penalty fee
our legal team will be in touch. Goodbye, then.
What was that?
After taking care of the penalties
Hongsung will enter the Chinese market before CGM.
We've already expanded to China.
Yes, but our China branch is practically
just a distribution channel for Korean brands.
So?
You suggest we bring foreign brands to China first?
Yes, sir.
We'll select the ones CGM is most afraid of
and Hongsung will plant our flag in China before CGM does.
Is that even possible?
Would global brands even want to team up with us
over CGM?
Maybe not if it was between us and CGM.
But what about Mantua?
CGM may be an industry giant
but they can't compare to Mantua.
Honestly, if we just look at perfume sales
Mantua is in a whole different class.
CGM's brands may do well in North America
but Mantua has European brands expanding worldwide.
They just dump inventory wholesale.
Will they consider retail?
What if we set everything up in China so they can sell wholesale?
It's not like Hongsung is saying we'll be their agency.
It's a win-win strategy if they just help us secure brands.
There's no reason not to do it.
If they do it, Mantua's brands will wholly become ours.
He's right.
In a fight between CGM and Mantua
- no brand would join CGM. - Right.
If we can bring Mantua to China
we will win.
So we'll get the penalties we're owed and win this futile fight too.
And those who left us
will have no choice but to renew contracts with us.
Yes, we can get even better terms.
This conversation
must stay between us.
Park Gi-tae, Lee Ji-hye.
- Yes? - Yes?
You two should be most careful.
People tend to spill when they suddenly get exclusive information.
Do you understand?
- Yes, ma'am. - Yes, we'll be careful.
- Mr. Gong. - Yes?
Starting tomorrow, withdraw from all stores requesting new contracts
and collect the penalty fees.
- Interior construction costs too. - Yes, ma'am.
And Mr. Gong.
Do whatever it takes to get Sponza on board.
That's our lifeline.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's call it a day.
Ms. Park has such an aura.
Ms. Park knows my name.
Mine too.
Hey, Ms. Park knows me better than I know myself.
I bet she knows you all better than you know yourselves.
Hurry up.
All right.
Here we are.
This dish is
roe, caviar, and truffle atop grilled blackthroat seaperch.
Wait, I'll set it down for you.
Thank you, sir.
Eat the roe first.
Then the caviar and the truffle.
All right.
How is it?
Wow, it's incredible.
Thank you.
Hongsung says they'll withdraw all their stores.
At this rate, my mall will be full of empty spots.
We'll fill those spots with even better terms.
Why are you worrying?
Change is a scary thing.
Even more so when there's no resistance to it.
Sir.
You have nothing to worry about.
Hongsung has no cards to play.
That's what makes it weirder.
I assumed they'd at least accept 20%.
They probably figure contract renewal won't be easy
and are trying to get their penalty fees instead.
Of course, they'll try to get their penalty fees.
But I saw it's not just us.
It looks like they're withdrawing
from every mall that requested a new contract.
This means Hongsung is getting out of the business.
They should, if they can't handle it.
What else can they do?
- Mr. Jeong. - Yes?
How long were you at Hongsung?
Eleven years.
During that time
how many crises did Hongsung face?
I'm not sure.
Hongsung won't fall this easily.
I know that better than you.
I admire your confidence
but don't get too complacent.
If things go wrong, we'll be taking a big hit.
Yes, sir. I understand.
NOAVILLA MALL CONTRACT TERMINATION NOTICE
DELMAR MALL CONTRACT TERMINATION NOTICE
VICE PRESIDENT KOO IN-MOCK
Come in.
You wanted to see me, sir?
What is all this?
We can't resolve this by clinging to them.
So you'll withdraw from everything?
Do you just want to shut down without a plan?
We have a plan, sir.
What is it?
I'm sorry for asking
but may I report to you at a later date?
You punk, what do you take me for?
Jeong Seon-hyuk offered our Finance Team's leader
the CFO position for CGM's Korea Branch.
- So? - If I were Jeong Seon-hyuk
the first person I would contact would be you, Mr. Koo.
Even if he meets with the malls as CEO
they'll still talk down to him
because he's still the same person, even with CGM backing him.
If he wants to talk with the malls on equal footing
he needs someone like you, don't you think?
So are you keeping it confidential even from me?
I'm sorry, sir.
Mr. Gong Eun-tae?
THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
TEAM 5 LEADER GONG EUN-TAE
Yes, what is it?
MY DAUGHTER
MOM
Hi, Mom. Where are you?
Yun-gyeong, are you at home?
Where else would I be?
You wanted to eat dinner together.
Right.
But I think I'll be a little late.
Unbelievable.
I told you I was just going to eat with Min-ji.
I'm sorry.
I planned to get home early
- but something came up... - Whatever.
Did I beg you to eat with me?
Why make a promise you can't keep?
So annoying.
And it's my birthday. Seriously?
Well, I really was trying to get home early.
Whatever, I'm going out.
Where?
Start eating with Dad. I'll be there soon.
Why would I eat with Dad?
I'm hanging up.
WHEN TURNING LEFT, YIELD TO PEDESTRIANS
Subtitles by Eunice Kim